<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Xiaomi Pad 7 Pro MIUI Updates Tracker by XiaomiFirmwareUpdater</title><link>https://xmfirmwareupdater.com/miui/muyu</link><description>Your best website to track MIUI ROM releases!</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>https://xmfirmwareupdater.com/images/xfu.png</url><title>Xiaomi Pad 7 Pro MIUI Updates Tracker by XiaomiFirmwareUpdater</title><link>https://xmfirmwareupdater.com/miui/muyu</link></image><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 04:43:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>MIUI OS2.0.7.0.VOYCNXM Fastboot update for Xiaomi Pad 7 Pro China</title><link>https://bkt-sgp-miui-ota-update-alisgp.oss-ap-southeast-1.aliyuncs.com/OS2.0.7.0.VOYCNXM/muyu_images_OS2.0.7.0.VOYCNXM_20241106.0000.00_15.0_cn_4eeb73204c.tgz</link><description>&lt;p&lt;b&gt;New Stable Fastboot update available!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Device:&lt;/b&gt; Xiaomi Pad 7 Pro China&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Codename:&lt;/b&gt; muyu&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Version:&lt;/b&gt; OS2.0.7.0.VOYCNXM | 15.0&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Size:&lt;/b&gt; 9.2 GB&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;MD5:&lt;/b&gt; 4eeb73204cc3353b8d9c7a917f3160cb&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Changelog:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;[System]&lt;br&gt;Updated the security patch to November 2024. Increased system security.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Download:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href='https://bkt-sgp-miui-ota-update-alisgp.oss-ap-southeast-1.aliyuncs.com/OS2.0.7.0.VOYCNXM/muyu_images_OS2.0.7.0.VOYCNXM_20241106.0000.00_15.0_cn_4eeb73204c.tgz'&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>MIUI OS2.0.7.0.VOYCNXM Recovery update for Xiaomi Pad 7 Pro China</title><link>https://bigota.d.miui.com/OS2.0.7.0.VOYCNXM/muyu-ota_full-OS2.0.7.0.VOYCNXM-user-15.0-eceeb8ff01.zip</link><description>&lt;p&lt;b&gt;New Stable Recovery update available!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Device:&lt;/b&gt; Xiaomi Pad 7 Pro China&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Codename:&lt;/b&gt; muyu&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Version:&lt;/b&gt; OS2.0.7.0.VOYCNXM | 15.0&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Size:&lt;/b&gt; 8.1 GB&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;MD5:&lt;/b&gt; eceeb8ff01de37c7747b47f868938e0f&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Changelog:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;[System]&lt;br&gt;Updated the security patch to November 2024. Increased system security.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Download:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href='https://bigota.d.miui.com/OS2.0.7.0.VOYCNXM/muyu-ota_full-OS2.0.7.0.VOYCNXM-user-15.0-eceeb8ff01.zip'&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Incremental Update:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href='https://bigota.d.miui.com/OS2.0.7.0.VOYCNXM/muyu-ota_incremental-OS2.0.6.0.VOYCNXM-OS2.0.7.0.VOYCNXM-user-15.0-41bf411b13.zip'&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>MIUI OS2.0.1.0.VOYCNXM Recovery update for Xiaomi Pad 7 Pro China</title><link>https://bigota.d.miui.com/OS2.0.1.0.VOYCNXM/muyu-ota_full-OS2.0.1.0.VOYCNXM-user-15.0-400e270942.zip</link><description>&lt;p&lt;b&gt;New Stable Beta Recovery update available!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Device:&lt;/b&gt; Xiaomi Pad 7 Pro China&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Codename:&lt;/b&gt; muyu&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Version:&lt;/b&gt; OS2.0.1.0.VOYCNXM | 15.0&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Size:&lt;/b&gt; 7.9 GB&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;MD5:&lt;/b&gt; 400e2709428d23cbf82813dbe922e2f1&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Changelog:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;[Alive Design Philosophy]&lt;br&gt;Alive Design Philosophy 2.0 unveils fresh, vibrant design across the whole system, making every interaction feel smooth and alive.&lt;br&gt;Artistic Lock screen brings new templates and effects inspired by classic designs, giving your phone a cinematic look every time you unlock it.&lt;br&gt;AI-generated dynamic wallpapers instantly bring static images to life.&lt;br&gt;With AI and reorganized collections, Gallery makes your memories even more vivid.&lt;br&gt;Real-time Weather Engine 2.0 shows you the sky and clouds just like in real life – even lets you see rainbows and the Milky Way.&lt;br&gt;The new Desktop calendar adds a touch of ritual to your day.&lt;br&gt;Updated Clock uses a more refined display structure for a more elegant, easy-to-read look.&lt;br&gt;Enhanced widgets allow you to customize and combine information on your Home screen for a more efficient, stylish experience.&lt;br&gt;A full-scale animation upgrade makes every interaction flow smoothly and feel stable, responsive, and comfortable.&lt;br&gt;[HyperCore]&lt;br&gt;Xiaomi HyperCore, Xiaomi's proprietary core technology platform, enhances performance, graphics, network, and security.&lt;br&gt;A new in-house microarchitecture scheduler manages tasks more efficiently.&lt;br&gt;New dynamic memory allows precise resource allocation, so apps start up faster.&lt;br&gt;Upgraded rendering for multitasking extends battery life.&lt;br&gt;Enhanced rendering pipeline boosts hardware performance for faster, more efficient visuals.&lt;br&gt;[HyperConnect]&lt;br&gt;Xiaomi HyperConnect offers upgraded device interconnectivity for a smoother experience.&lt;br&gt;With upgraded Home Screen+, you can drag phone apps onto Xiaomi tablets or add them as native apps.&lt;br&gt;The upgraded cross-device camera allows you to use two cameras simultaneously for multi-angle live streaming.&lt;br&gt;Shared clipboard allows you to batch copy text for easier multi-device sharing.&lt;br&gt;Take document editing to a new level with over 100 supported file formats, including documents, spreadsheets, and presentations across devices.&lt;br&gt;Smart home upgrades improve the consistency of control experience of various terminal devices, covering Xiaomi Smart Hub, Home screen widgets, and the Xiaomi Home app.&lt;br&gt;Enhanced interconnectivity for phones, wearables, and cars, adding 62 new ways for your devices to interact with each other.&lt;br&gt;[HyperAI]&lt;br&gt;Xiaomi HyperAI reshapes system apps with AI, enhancing productivity and usability and creating a dynamic, ever-evolving user experience.&lt;br&gt;Generate, summarize, expand, polish, and correct text wherever you are with AI writing.&lt;br&gt;With AI art, you can select parts of an image to generate stunning artworks in multiple styles, with options for using references and partial edits.&lt;br&gt;Now, AI can recognize audio and transcribe in real time, summarize automatically, and mark speakers.&lt;br&gt;With AI search, you can finds photos, videos, messages, notes, and recordings accurately.&lt;br&gt;Upgraded translation and interpretation features introduced with AI Interpreter.&lt;br&gt;AI allows you to add effects to video calls with simple hand gestures.&lt;br&gt;AI data security&lt;br&gt;End-to-end encryption is provided for sensitive data.&lt;br&gt;Trusted computing architecture for data security across devices and cloud.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Download:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href='https://bigota.d.miui.com/OS2.0.1.0.VOYCNXM/muyu-ota_full-OS2.0.1.0.VOYCNXM-user-15.0-400e270942.zip'&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>