<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" version="2.0"><channel><title>Xiaomi Pad 7S Pro 12.5 MIUI Updates Tracker by XiaomiFirmwareUpdater</title><link>https://xmfirmwareupdater.com/miui/violin</link><description>Your best website to track MIUI ROM releases!</description><docs>http://www.rssboard.org/rss-specification</docs><generator>python-feedgen</generator><image><url>https://xmfirmwareupdater.com/images/xfu.png</url><title>Xiaomi Pad 7S Pro 12.5 MIUI Updates Tracker by XiaomiFirmwareUpdater</title><link>https://xmfirmwareupdater.com/miui/violin</link></image><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Nov 2025 04:17:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><item><title>MIUI OS2.0.215.0.VOTCNXM Fastboot update for Xiaomi Pad 7S Pro 12.5 China</title><link>https://bkt-sgp-miui-ota-update-alisgp.oss-ap-southeast-1.aliyuncs.com/OS2.0.215.0.VOTCNXM/violin-images-OS2.0.215.0.VOTCNXM-user-20250917.0000.00-15.0-cn-67e164372d.tgz</link><description>&lt;p&lt;b&gt;New Stable Fastboot update available!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Device:&lt;/b&gt; Xiaomi Pad 7S Pro 12.5 China&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Codename:&lt;/b&gt; violin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Version:&lt;/b&gt; OS2.0.215.0.VOTCNXM | 15.0&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Size:&lt;/b&gt; 9.6 GB&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;MD5:&lt;/b&gt; 67e164372df5a3b688a537d052b3fe2d&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Changelog:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;[System]&lt;br&gt;Updated the security patch to September 2025. Increased system security.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Download:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href='https://bkt-sgp-miui-ota-update-alisgp.oss-ap-southeast-1.aliyuncs.com/OS2.0.215.0.VOTCNXM/violin-images-OS2.0.215.0.VOTCNXM-user-20250917.0000.00-15.0-cn-67e164372d.tgz'&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>MIUI OS3.0.6.0.WOTCNXM Recovery update for Xiaomi Pad 7S Pro 12.5 China</title><link>https://bigota.d.miui.com/OS3.0.6.0.WOTCNXM/violin-ota_full-OS3.0.6.0.WOTCNXM-user-16.0-c9a2a55dc0.zip</link><description>&lt;p&lt;b&gt;New Stable Recovery update available!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Device:&lt;/b&gt; Xiaomi Pad 7S Pro 12.5 China&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Codename:&lt;/b&gt; violin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Version:&lt;/b&gt; OS3.0.6.0.WOTCNXM | 16.0&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Size:&lt;/b&gt; 8.3 GB&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;MD5:&lt;/b&gt; c9a2a55dc0c0a9cf4f4ab5b2309b35b0&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Changelog:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;[Basic experience]&lt;br&gt;Smoother and more stable&lt;br&gt;Performance enhancements:&lt;br&gt;Optimization: Refined compiler instructions enhance performance and responsiveness while lowering power use.&lt;br&gt;Optimization: Improved memory allocation and recovery increases available system memory.&lt;br&gt;Optimization: Improved integrated frequency scheduling boosts system efficiency and reduces power consumption.&lt;br&gt;Optimization: Improved short-video playback efficiency for better battery life.&lt;br&gt; &lt;br&gt;Optimized graphics:&lt;br&gt;A new window-rendering mechanism reduces graphics-rendering load.&lt;br&gt;  &lt;br&gt;Smoother system animations:&lt;br&gt;Optimization: Fine-tuned animations across 100+ system scenes for smoother, more natural motion.&lt;br&gt;[Revamped visuals]&lt;br&gt;Cleaner, more refined visuals throughout.&lt;br&gt;Redesigned Home screen icons now look sharper and more detailed.&lt;br&gt;The status bar has a new, cleaner design that's more refined and easier to read.&lt;br&gt;A new design system improves color comfort, unifies rounded corners across the entire system, and makes controls easier to use for a more consistent look and feel.&lt;br&gt;A new large-clock Lock screen adds more depth and layers to the layout.&lt;br&gt;New AI-powered dynamic wallpapers turn static images into dynamic ones with a single tap.&lt;br&gt;A new all-in-one editor allows you to adjust both the Home screen and Lock screen wallpapers at the same time.&lt;br&gt;[Comprehensive system app optimization]&lt;br&gt;Interaction with apps has become more intuitive and direct.&lt;br&gt;Gallery:&lt;br&gt;New: New Gallery widgets allow you to select your preferred collections for display.&lt;br&gt;New: You can pin albums now to have quick access to your favorite photos anytime.&lt;br&gt;Optimization: Improved search for quicker, more accurate results for photos.&lt;br&gt;   &lt;br&gt;Calendar:&lt;br&gt;New: Week view gives you a clear look at your weekly schedule.&lt;br&gt;Optimization: Improved month-view visuals give you clearer highlights for holidays and important events.&lt;br&gt;     &lt;br&gt;Recorder:&lt;br&gt;New: With technical term and dialect recognition, your transcriptions have become even more accurate.&lt;br&gt;New: Structured summaries let you review recorded content more efficiently.&lt;br&gt;Optimization: Accurate start page categories let you locate recordings faster with icons.&lt;br&gt;Optimization: Improved playback brings you smart noise reduction for clearer voices.&lt;br&gt;       &lt;br&gt;Other improvements:&lt;br&gt;New: Copied text in certain scenarios now opens the related app directly.&lt;br&gt;New: Alarms can now be used with your work shift schedule.&lt;br&gt;Optimization: Improved Child mode with unified time tracking across devices, eye care features, and better protection tools.&lt;br&gt;[Xiaomi Hyper XiaoAi]&lt;br&gt;Smoother. Effortless.&lt;br&gt;More convenient interface:&lt;br&gt;New: Now you can launch apps quickly by typing their initials.&lt;br&gt;Optimization: Improved wake-up animations and interface.&lt;br&gt;        &lt;br&gt;All-new Xiaomi Hyper XiaoAi suggestions:&lt;br&gt;New: When you wake your assistant, scene-aware suggestions appear with one-tap access to relevant features, no typing needed.&lt;br&gt;         &lt;br&gt;Circle to select with Xiaomi Hyper XiaoAi:&lt;br&gt;Circle to select items as soon as your voice assistant reacts. Now it understands on-screen content and can answer questions or perform actions. After circling, it can also share a screenshot.&lt;br&gt;          &lt;br&gt;Translate images effortlessly:&lt;br&gt;You can translate the content captured by your camera or seen on your screen with continuous translation as you scroll.&lt;br&gt;            &lt;br&gt;DeepThink mode:&lt;br&gt;Get in-depth analysis of complex questions and generate structured research reports using multi-dimensional information.&lt;br&gt;[Interconnectivity]&lt;br&gt;Cross-ecosystem interconnectivity offers deep compatibility with the Apple ecosystem.&lt;br&gt;Casting:&lt;br&gt;You can now extend windows for screen mirroring and select which app window to cast.&lt;br&gt;               &lt;br&gt;Cross-device unlocking:&lt;br&gt;Use the fingerprint or password on your Xiaomi tablet to unlock your Xiaomi phone.&lt;br&gt;[Privacy and security]&lt;br&gt;Enhanced protection keeps your data private and safe.&lt;br&gt;Private access lets apps access only the data you choose, giving you full control over your privacy.&lt;br&gt;* This feature requires developer support.&lt;br&gt;The system's privacy and password features have been redesigned with a cleaner, fresher interface.&lt;br&gt;Advanced data protection now uses post-quantum encryption to keep personal data even more secure.&lt;br&gt;                    &lt;br&gt;Find device:&lt;br&gt;New Lost mode lets you locate your device once it's turned on.&lt;br&gt;Now you can locate your device even when it's offline or powered off.&lt;br&gt;[Other]&lt;br&gt;Visit our website to learn more: https://hyperos.mi.com/&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Download:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href='https://bigota.d.miui.com/OS3.0.6.0.WOTCNXM/violin-ota_full-OS3.0.6.0.WOTCNXM-user-16.0-c9a2a55dc0.zip'&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title>MIUI OS2.0.203.0.VOTCNXM Recovery update for Xiaomi Pad 7S Pro 12.5 China</title><link>https://bigota.d.miui.com/OS2.0.203.0.VOTCNXM/violin-ota_full-OS2.0.203.0.VOTCNXM-user-15.0-701c5549f6.zip</link><description>&lt;p&lt;b&gt;New Stable Beta Recovery update available!&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Device:&lt;/b&gt; Xiaomi Pad 7S Pro 12.5 China&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Codename:&lt;/b&gt; violin&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Version:&lt;/b&gt; OS2.0.203.0.VOTCNXM | 15.0&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Size:&lt;/b&gt; 7.9 GB&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;MD5:&lt;/b&gt; 701c5549f6d3e60cef9172ec6187b80a&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Changelog:&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;[Alive Design Philosophy]&lt;br&gt;Alive Design Philosophy unveils fresh, vibrant design across the whole system, making every interaction feel smooth and alive.&lt;br&gt;All-new Artistic Lock screen:&lt;br&gt;Artistic Lock screen brings new templates and effects inspired by classic designs, giving your device a cinematic look every time you unlock it.&lt;br&gt;AI dynamic wallpapers:&lt;br&gt;AI-generated dynamic wallpapers bring static images to life.&lt;br&gt;All-new Gallery:&lt;br&gt;With AI and reorganized collections, Gallery makes your memories even more vivid.&lt;br&gt;All-new Weather&lt;br&gt;Real-time Weather Engine 2.0 shows you the sky and clouds just like in real life – even lets you see rainbows and the Milky Way.&lt;br&gt;All-new Calendar:&lt;br&gt;The new Desktop calendar adds a touch of ritual to your day.&lt;br&gt;All-new Clock:&lt;br&gt;Updated Clock uses a more refined display structure for a more elegant, easy-to-read look.&lt;br&gt;Updated widgets:&lt;br&gt;Enhanced widgets allow you to customize and combine information on your Home screen for a more efficient, stylish experience.&lt;br&gt;Updated animations:&lt;br&gt;A full-scale animation upgrade makes every interaction flow smoothly and feel stable, responsive, and comfortable.&lt;br&gt;[Xiaomi HyperCore]&lt;br&gt;Xiaomi HyperCore, Xiaomi's proprietary core technology platform, enhances performance, graphics, network, and security.&lt;br&gt;New microarchitecture scheduler:&lt;br&gt;A new in-house microarchitecture scheduler manages tasks more efficiently.&lt;br&gt;New dynamic memory:&lt;br&gt;New technology allows precise resource allocation, so apps start up faster.&lt;br&gt;Storage 2.0:&lt;br&gt;Improved file loading for long-term smooth performance.&lt;br&gt;Upgraded rendering:&lt;br&gt;Upgraded rendering for multitasking extends battery life.&lt;br&gt;Heterogeneous computing:&lt;br&gt;Enhanced rendering pipeline boosts hardware performance for faster, more efficient visuals.&lt;br&gt;Enhanced wireless compatibility:&lt;br&gt;Enhanced wireless compatibility boosts network stability for more reliable connections.&lt;br&gt;[Xiaomi HyperConnect]&lt;br&gt;Upgraded cross-device connectivity framework.&lt;br&gt;Upgraded Home screen+:&lt;br&gt;You can drag phone apps onto Xiaomi tablets or add them as native apps.&lt;br&gt;Updated cross-device camera:&lt;br&gt;The upgraded cross-device camera allows you to use two cameras simultaneously for multi-angle live streaming.&lt;br&gt;Updated shared clipboard:&lt;br&gt;Shared clipboard allows you to batch copy text for easier multi-device sharing.&lt;br&gt;Smart home devices:&lt;br&gt;Smart home upgrades improve the consistency of control experience of various terminal devices, covering Xiaomi Smart Hub, Home screen widgets, and the Xiaomi Home app.&lt;br&gt;Documents:&lt;br&gt;Take document editing to a new level with over 100 supported file formats, including documents, spreadsheets, and presentations across devices.&lt;br&gt;[Xiaomi HyperAI]&lt;br&gt;Xiaomi HyperAI reshapes system apps with AI, enhancing productivity and usability and creating a dynamic, ever-evolving user experience.&lt;br&gt;All-new AI writing:&lt;br&gt;Generate, summarize, expand, polish, and correct text wherever you are with AI writing.&lt;br&gt;All-new AI art:&lt;br&gt;With AI art, you can select parts of an image to generate stunning artworks in multiple styles, with options for using references and partial edits.&lt;br&gt;AI audio recognition:&lt;br&gt;Now, AI can recognize audio and transcribe in real time, summarize automatically, and mark speakers.&lt;br&gt;All-new AI search:&lt;br&gt;With AI search, you can find photos, videos, messages, notes, and recordings accurately.&lt;br&gt;AI Interpreter:&lt;br&gt;Upgraded translation and interpretation features.&lt;br&gt;AI data security:&lt;br&gt;End-to-end encryption is provided for sensitive data.&lt;br&gt;Trusted computing architecture:&lt;br&gt;Ensure the security of your data across devices and cloud.&lt;br&gt;[System]&lt;br&gt;New: Support for one-tap clipboard clearing&lt;br&gt;[Xiaomi Hyper XiaoAi]&lt;br&gt;Your smart personal assistant&lt;br&gt;· New visuals with multiple ways to activate the assistant anytime you need it.&lt;br&gt;Multimodal interaction: Perceive the world around you with your camera and easily recognize objects that appear on your screen.&lt;br&gt;· Improved search: Supports natural language searches for photos, videos, documents, notes, and recordings.&lt;br&gt;Smart scenes: Seamlessly integrates system features, letting you perform complex tasks with a single step. This feature also learns your patterns to offer helpful services proactively.&lt;br&gt;[Mi Share]&lt;br&gt;New: Support for file transfers between different devices using different Xiaomi Accounts&lt;br&gt;[Lock screen]&lt;br&gt;New: Eastern aesthetics lock screen templates&lt;br&gt;[Status bar, Notification shade]&lt;br&gt;New: Some status bar icons now support custom display&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Download:&lt;/b&gt; &lt;a href='https://bigota.d.miui.com/OS2.0.203.0.VOTCNXM/violin-ota_full-OS2.0.203.0.VOTCNXM-user-15.0-701c5549f6.zip'&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>